To be continued...
30 years ago, an unprecedented disaster called a spatial quake assaulted our world.
The female lifeforms which caused them were called spirits,
but whether the catastrophes were unintentional or planned was unclear.
The very existence of these spirits was kept secret from the public.
But I, Shido Itsuka, know all about them.
Go on! You've got it tasted, Shido!
There's no need to be shy! Come on, eat it!
And this is what?
It's stew. Obviously.
We each had different ideas about what we should make for you, so we just combined them all.
Well, I really appreciate the thought. What the heck did you put in there to make it look like that?
We kind of went all out this time. Everyone got together and tossed in their favorite foods.
Oh, well, that's incredibly thoughtful.
Isn't that just the most wonderful thing you've ever heard of?
Go on, eat some while it's still hot!
Hey, Coterie, you should contribute, too. Go ahead and make a little offering to the banquet.
Oh, we keep making it better and better!
And the color is even more beautiful!
Holy crap!
Well, how is it?
Surprisingly good.
Yay!
Look at you!
See, I knew Yuzuru's fried chicken would be able to tie all those flavors together.
Negative. It was Kaguya's pork cutlet that did it. It's what made the broth so savory.
What? Nah, it was your chicken.
No way. It was Kaguya's. You two will never change, will you?
Maybe we should just recognize it as the miraculous collaboration that it is and leave it at that.
On TV, they said stew's good no matter what you put in it, and now we know it's true!
Miraculous is right. For something that looks like this to end up being edible at all.
Such a bummer that Miku couldn't be here to join us for dinner. Just part of being an idol, I guess.
Oh, darling!
He rang!
Surprise!
I heard you calling out to me through the ether. I couldn't resist, so here I am!
Miku Izuyo's spirit idol has now arrived.
Miku?
Wait. How are you singing live on TV?
Oh, please. That was pre-recorded.
Anyway, what are you crazy bunch up to?
It kind of looks like a party with all of you together like this.
Oh!
As a matter of fact, now that I think of it, today's actually my birthday.
Don't worry. All I want from each one of you is a great big kissy-wissy.
What are you doing?
Defense. Kaguya barrier.
Wait!
Stop, Miku! Get right back inside that TV!
Come on, don't be shocked!
You're still the Kaguya barrier.
Oh, now I get it. So that's why you're eating such a strange-smelling stew.
Yeah. Anyway, it's really good to have you here, Miku. Here you go. Careful, though. It's pretty hot.
My, it really is a unique color. Well, here goes nothing.
Are you okay? That's why I warned you.
Oh, darling. You'll never believe this, but I seem to have burned my poor lips.
I'm afraid unless you kiss them, they won't ever heal.
I know what you're trying to do, Miku. That's not even how burns work.
My lips hurt, too. Such pain. It seems I've also been burned by stew. I think I require urgent care.
Hey, no bear!
Hey, Shido, don't forget Yoshido's lips.
Shido! Look at that! I accidentally burned my lips, too.
You guys, come on.
My brother!
I think I did too, for real!
Why'd your ribbons just turn white?
Aw, I hope everyone's gonna be okay.
Don't you worry, I know the perfect thing to make you all feel better right away.
Hey!
Hmm?
What? Origami?
I've prepared a stew for you, too.
Wow, did you really?
Uh, thanks a lot.
The body parts from a turtle, scorpion, and seal, boiled in an energy drink.
Next time we meet, please tell me your thoughts on how you liked it.
So, though rife with culinary drama, life is actually pretty good right now.
Shido.
It's time.
Let's get on with the next state, then, shall we?
You all set down there?
Yep.
Whenever you're ready.
What a weird place.
It's so creepy.
This park has been completely abandoned ever since the Great Spatial Quake.
It's just far enough away from the redevelopment that it's remained untouched to this day.
So, it's just as it was 30 years ago.
The spirit we tracked moved from the Spatial Quake's origin site to somewhere around that area.
You need to make contact before the AST shows up.
Roger that.
The heck?
What is it?
Strange buildings for a park.
This can't be what it used to look like, right?
It's faint, but we are detecting some spirit waves.
Everything you're seeing was manifested by a spirit's powers.
Are you hearing that?
Shido.
The spirit we're after is close by for sure.
Oh.
What a rare sight.
Usually when I'm pulled here, I never run into anyone but the AST.
So, this is a pleasant surprise.
There's nothing for you to be afraid of.
It's not like I'm going to eat you or anything.
Uh, no, I'm just...
Hey, you're actually kind of cute, aren't you?
What are you doing in a place like this?
Aren't there alarms that warn you to take shelter whenever a spirit appears?
Well, yeah, but...
Shido, our choices!
Everyone, decide!
Well, this one was pretty straightforward.
It's gotta be one, right?
Without knowing her temperament, it makes sense to keep it direct.
Wrong!
We should go with choice number two.
This spirit's a big sister type.
You might not expect it, but Shido can really tickle those maternal instincts.
Mm-hmm, mm-hmm.
I'll admit there's some truth to that.
Though I'm kind of shocked.
Not a single person chose option three.
I thought I could at least count on Kamazuki to pick it as a joke.
Alas, her boobs bounce too much.
My tastes tend to veer toward the budding ones.
Now, if we were talking about licking the back of her knee, I might have to reconsider.
What's the matter, young one?
Uh, well, I, um, the thing is, I don't really know.
I barely escaped.
Then I ended up here.
Oh, is that so?
What's your name, love?
Shido Itsuka.
Shido, then.
That's a really cute name.
You can call me Natsumi.
Although some of you humans prefer calling me witch if what I hear is correct.
Hello, Miss Natsumi.
That sounds so formal.
Natsumi is fine.
Come here, Shido.
Big sis here wants to ask you a little something special.
So may I?
Sure, yeah, go ahead.
What do you think?
Do you find me pretty?
Well, yeah.
I think you're very pretty.
Yes, knew it!
Tell me this.
Specifically, what is it you find pretty about me?
Let's see.
Your sparkling eyes.
The way your nose is so straight.
Your cool, feminine style.
Love that.
Keep going.
Your hair.
It looks so silky.
Yes!
Shido kid, you're right on the money.
I was right.
I knew that this me was beautiful.
Shido!
A.S.T.
Incoming!
Oh, dear.
This is bad.
You'll be okay.
Let's get to work.
Pondale!
This is so weird.
Take this!
Huh?
Let's go, Shido.
I think we should escape while we still can.
You're gonna keep giving your big sis lots more compliments, though, aren't you?
Uh, yeah.
I don't mind doing that, but...
The surveillance camera stopped working.
We're on it.
Didn't see that coming.
You okay, Natsumi?
Shido, this is not good.
Natsumi's happiness meter is currently plummeting.
You saw, right?
Huh?
Don't try to play dumb.
I know you saw my...
Unforgivable.
And you won't get away with it.
Shido Ichika!
Heed my words.
Your life is about to be over!
Why the heck did she just fly off like that?
Hmm...
Wow, it's already lunchtime?
I didn't expect those strategy meetings for dealing with Natsumi would go all night.
Hey, what's up?
How dare you show your face, Shido Ichika?
You seriously have zero shame, don't you?
That is so lame!
I don't understand.
What are you talking about?
You have some nerve playing dumb.
Making lewd passes at Sweet Eye.
Embarrassing the hell out of Maya and me.
And not just that.
Even Touka was a victim of your heinous crimes.
That's so lame!
Wait, hold on a second.
First of all, I was busy this morning and just now got to school.
You should learn when to fess up.
Shido, listen.
What's done is done.
But you shouldn't just pretend like it never happened.
Jeez.
At the very least, next time, give me a little heads up.
That way I can prepare myself a bit.
No, look!
I'm telling you, I really did it!
Origami!
Please, don't tell me.
I did something terrible to you, too!
You did nothing.
Thank goodness.
What do you think you're doing, Origami Tomiichi?
Well, that was weird.
I thought you were glad that I didn't do anything before.
Right.
So I could have you do it right now.
Yes.
I want you to do those things to me, too.
Push me up against the wall.
Lift up my chin.
Whisper sweet words in my ear while you gently lift my skirt.
Then we'll exchange a deep, romantic kiss.
You'll pull off my clothes, take my innocence as a woman.
Then you'll leave your everlasting mark on me, imbued within my body.
Hold on!
He hasn't done that stuff with anyone yet!
I'm yours, Shido.
Do it.
Look, this is kind of a lot.
Aha!
There you are!
I'll give you this.
It's a ballsy move, sticking around school.
Small warning.
You'll pay for what you've done here today.
Oh, man.
Not you, too.
Are you saying I somehow managed to assault both of you as well?
Feigning ignorance?
Let me tell you something.
If you don't give me those panties back, you're in trouble.
We hold grudges.
Especially when someone throws water on me while yelling that you have a wet t-shirt fetish.
Huh?
But I would never do that!
It's as iffy has no boundaries at all.
No kidding.
This goes beyond playing around.
He's so lame.
In any case, we won't stand for this.
Do you hear me?
It's a crime to defy BMI, which means you're going to have to pay for this!
To be specific, I'll be stripping off your undies.
Response.
Additionally, I shall use the spray bottle until your entire naked body is soaking wet.
No!
That's not fair!
I didn't do anything!
Oh, you're here.
Look, I have no desire to become a bride.
But after what you did, I think I have to.
Wait, do you even miss Tom?
Hey, Itsuka.
About earlier.
Are you actually serious?
I mean, I don't know what to say.
You've got to be jacked!
It's so lame!
Hold on!
I'm confused!
It's so lame!
What in the world is happening around here?
Wait!
Hey there!
That was quick.
I don't get it.
Who are you?
The one who was having all sorts of nasty fun with your friends while you were away.
Yeah, I figured.
Who the hell are you?
What are you after by impersonating me?
Is that funny?
It really is, as a matter of fact.
Because you see...
Somehow, dumb little Shido still hasn't managed to figure it out.
You're not Sumi, aren't you?
Ding, ding, ding!
Well done!
Surely by now you must have realized why I've been impersonating you here at school, right?
Don't say it.
Shido Itsuka!
Heed my words!
Your life is about to be over!
So did you do all those crazy things just so I wouldn't be able to live here anymore?
Headiful.
I'm docking points.
Fine.
Tell me why.
Shido, don't you think it'll be a great adventure, having two of you out in the world?
Think of the fun.
We can see how far everyone's willing to go.
From now on, I think I'll take over as Shido, okay?
Don't worry, I have quite the observant eye.
I won't goof around like I did with everybody today.
That way, even if you're dead, no one will suspect a thing.
Look, Natsumi, this is...
Get off me!
I was here first!
If anyone is going to track down Shido, it's gonna be me!
No, I'm afraid you're mistaken.
I won't allow you to find him.
There are two Shidos?
Explain yourselves now.
Toka, Origami, listen to me!
This guy...
This guy is an imposter!
He's the fake who's been running around all day harassing my friends!
Don't be fooled!
I'm the real one!
You're so full of it!
It's obviously me!
So I guess...
Now we figure out who's the real Shido.
It's a baffling turn.
But, if I had to guess...
You must be the imposter!
But how could you guys possibly think that?
I'm the real Shido!
You are most definitely not!
Sure, you look exactly like Shido, but he has a totally different smell!
If you were here alone, you might have been able to deceive me.
But standing next to the real one makes the choice obvious.
For example, compared to the real Shido, you blink 50 milliseconds faster, and your center of gravity is angled 0.2 degrees to the left.
There's no mistaking it!
What is wrong with these girls?
They're all messed up!
Well, I wouldn't even try to deny that.
This is just unbelievable!
Unbelievable!
You ruined it!
Wait, who?
Unforgivable!
Not only was my secret exposed, which is unacceptable, but you also saw right through my flawless disguise!
Never happened!
I will never acknowledge this day!
And don't think you two are off the hook!
Unforgivable!
Hey, wait!
Shido, who in the world was that, anyway?
And what's your relationship with her?
Oh, that's... I mean, I don't know...
It's been five days.
No movement from Natsumi at all.
What is she planning to do?
Sorry, but you totally deserved that.
Kotari, seriously, why?
Because you screwed up somehow!
For whatever reason, Natsumi now views you as her enemy!
You'll never be able to seal her power unless you can raise her happiness level.
Yeah, I know that stuff already!
Of course, there's really no knowing when she might next appear to you.
Look, though. This showed up in the mail today.
What is it?
I don't know. I haven't opened it yet.
But I did check to make sure it was safe.
At least you can rest easy.
It shouldn't go boom or anything like that.
This is...
Shida, what's wrong?
Twelve photos...
And this.
I'm here among your friends.
Can you take a guess which one I am?
Before everyone else disappears, too.
Natsumi.
What the heck's that mean?
Well, if we take the message at face value...
Natsumi's using her powers to impersonate someone.
And we've got twelve guesses as to who that might be.
One of your friends.
Yeah, but who?
I don't know.
But it's possible she's pretending to be me, too.
Shida, this is a direct challenge from Natsumi.
Unless you decipher who she's impersonating...
I imagine that your friends will continue disappearing.
Find her, Shida.
Before we are all gone.
Dating.
So sweet.
Agonizing.
And torturous.
The curtain has been raised.
Now.
For the third time.
Let's check.
Outro.
Thank you.